export const questions = [
    {
        question: "Who created React.js?",
        options: ["Jordan Mike", "Jordan Walke", "Tim Lee", "Jordan Lee"],
        answer: "Jordan Walke"
    },
    {
        question: "How many elements can a valid react component return?",
        options: ["1", "2", "3", "4"],
        answer: "1"
    },
    {
        question: "Among the corner which is a must-have for every ReactJS component?",
        options: ["renderComponent", "SetinitialComponent", "Render", "All of the above"],
        answer: "renderComponent"
    },
    {
        question: "Total ways of defining variables in ES6 is?",
        options: ["1", "2", "3", "3"],
        answer: "3"
    },
    {
        question: "Using which of the following command can prevent default behaviour at in react?",
        options: ["preventDefault()", "avoidDefault()", "revokeDefault()", "All of the above"],
        answer: "preventDefault()"
    },
    {
        question: "What are arbitrary inputs of components in react also known as?",
        options: ["Elements", "Props", "Keys", "Ref"],
        answer: "Props"
    },
    {
        question: "What is ReactJS mainly used for building?",
        options: ["Database", "Connectivity", "User interface", "Design platform"],
        answer: "User interface"
    },
    {
        question: "What is used to handle code-splitting?",
        options: ["React.lazy", "React.memo", "React.fallback", "React.split"],
        answer: "React.lazy"
    },
    {
        question: "Which company developed ReactJS?",
        options: ["Apple", "Twitter", "Facebook", "Google"],
        answer: "Facebook"
    },
    {
        question: "Which of the following port is the default where webpack-dev-server runs?",
        options: ["3000", "3306", "3030", "8080"],
        answer: "8080"
    }
];
